<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/">
    <channel>
        <title>Joy Neop</title>
        <atom:link href="http://joyneop.xyz/blog/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/</link>
        <description>Do what you want to do. Be what you want to be.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>July 30, 2014 09:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
        <sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
        <generator>http://joyneop.github.io/blog/</generator>
        <item>
            <title>Woodstocky</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=108</link>
            <pubDate>July 30, 2014 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=108</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201407300001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>青春路上</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=107</link>
            <pubDate>July 12, 2014 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=107</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201407120001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Visionary</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=106</link>
            <pubDate>July 10, 2014 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=106</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201407100001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Auromna</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=105</link>
            <pubDate>July 5, 2014 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=105</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201407050001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Rainy Lily</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=104</link>
            <pubDate>June 25, 2014 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=104</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201406250001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Pink Wall</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=103</link>
            <pubDate>June 24, 2014 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=103</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201406240001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Freshness</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=102</link>
            <pubDate>June 24, 2014 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=102</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>生命是有鮮度的。即使身體構造允許，也無法活數千年。在鮮度耗盡時，會開始厭倦活著。厭倦所擁有的生命。</p>
<p>然而，在耗盡鮮度前便已得到安息的人，並不擁有真正的幸福。求生本能，鮮度消耗，一邊是生命誕生之初的原始動力，一邊是無法阻擋的自然衰敗。它們驅使著人，在鮮度殆盡時陷入精神錯亂，在鮮度歸零時既不心甘情願又不心懷眷戀地結束生命。</p>
<p>身體構造阻止我活到宇宙終點，求生本能阻止我主動結束生命，物理規律阻止我抹除我的出生。</p>
<p>終將死亡，為何要有生命?</p>
<p>無法維持鮮度，為何要讓我存在?</p>
<p>隨機碰撞製造出的生命，一開始便沒有意義。生命的意志，也不會接受創造者給予的意義。</p>
<p>被囚禁在「活著的人」這個尷尬的狀態中，永生不得，自殺不得。即使相信可以順利地在開始厭倦活著之前自然死亡。</p>
<p>唯有死亡，方能安息。</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Mortality</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=101</link>
            <pubDate>April 25, 2014 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=101</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>The contract with Mephisto enabled our ancients to evolve, by forcing them die. Death made livings to breed, thus many, but few among all, mutations were selected by the nature to be spread.</p>
<p>Thanks to Mephisto, humans have become wise life. Thanks to Mephisto, livings have kept evolving. Thanks to Mephisto, I have been born.</p>
<p>Thanks to Mephisto, I can think about life and death.</p>
<p>Sacrifice every individual's respective life, to redeem entire species' long living.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Way To 42</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=100</link>
            <pubDate>February 27, 2014 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=100</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>When I gaze at other designers' work, I find me less professional. When I read other programmers' codes, I find me less talented. But I do not have to compare me with them, for I seek much much more.</p>
<p>Great revolutions never come from one single breakthrough. Multiplied UNIX by open source, Linus and Richard got Linux. Multiplied multi-touch screen by specifically redesigned human-interface, Steve, Scott and Jonathan got iPhone. It is not simply adding one onto another, or plus, it is multiplying. Combining is much much more than simply mixing.</p>
<p>This is also true for human individual development, I think, besides for human society. As a designer, I may or may not be greatly outstanding though professional enough, but what if I am also good at programming as same as a graduate from Computer Science major? What if I can also do globalization work for China market? What if I can be glue in a team? What if I can manage both products and visual identity?</p>
<p>I may or may not be the best, but at least I can be unique. My value is the product of various factors with their respective exponents, obvious or potential, such as designing skills, programming skills, photography skills, literature knowledge, traveling experience, cultural background, ability of associating, and much much more. Therefore I can change the world, at least a small part in my domain, in my own way, with my own methodology. Everyone has his own way which cannot be outlined in advance by prior people, and thus everyone explores his own way. It is the way to explore. It is the way to extreme. It is the way to 42.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Starting AP</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=99</link>
            <pubDate>February 11, 2014 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=99</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>To save money on education, I have decided to take AP tests to get credit redemption. So I arrived in Dalian and started to study for AP. Take a series of courses for AP Physics B and Calculus BC.</p>
<p>I rent an underground room for temporarily living near by Ealing, the private educational institute which provides courses for SAT, AP and others. And it was founded by a friend of my aunt. Though no discount offered, she and one of her staff handled my college application thus I can concentrate on my own work.</p>
<p>The room is too cold to sleep in unless electric heating added. Yet the real problem is, there is no space for a desk so I cannot write in the room. Now I am writing in KFC.</p>
<p>The location is quite convenient, because it is near to both Ealing and downtown. </p>

]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Avatar: Rose</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=98</link>
            <pubDate>February 6, 2014 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=98</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201402060002.jpg">

]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Rose</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=97</link>
            <pubDate>February 6, 2014 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=97</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201402060001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Avatar: Chinese New Year</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=96</link>
            <pubDate>January 28, 2014 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=96</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201401280001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Macintosh, Thank You</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=95</link>
            <pubDate>January 24, 2014 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=95</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>30 years have passed since Steve Jobs introduced Macintosh to the world, and so far both Macintosh and Apple have been greatly appreciated around the world. Especially, I have benefited considerably from Macintosh, Apple, and Steve Jobs.</p>
<p>Thanks to my decision in later 2010 to get a Mac instead of a PC, which looks really profound now. Therefore, I got amazed by both the graceful hardware and the powerful software. It was the first time that I understood how surprising the combination of humanity and technology can be. Thanks to such experience, I eventually decided to be a designer in UI, though not only UI. I feel like managing everything in my own mind. My first Macintosh was the initial acceleration.</p>
<p>Macintosh is the symbol of that stage and an essential milestone along personal electronic devices' development, where most modern genius are spending their intelligence on, where I will also take part in. Hard to imagine what if I didn't decide to get a Mac. Hard to imagine what if I get a Mac more later. Hard to imagine what if I failed in getting a computer.</p>
<p>Therefore, I appreciate Macintosh much more than others do. My appreciating is beyond admiring, but acknowledging.</p>
<p>An essential encounter, in not only my life, but also this era.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Happy New Year 2014</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=94</link>
            <pubDate>January 1, 2014 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=94</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201401010001.jpg">
<img src="./img/0000201401010002.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>My Christmas Homepage</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=93</link>
            <pubDate>December 24, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=93</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201312240003.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Avatar: Christmas</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=92</link>
            <pubDate>December 24, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=92</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201312240002.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BBS Signature Line: iOS 7 (Version 2)</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=91</link>
            <pubDate>December 24, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=91</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201312240001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Milestone</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=90</link>
            <pubDate>December 16, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=90</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>After having taken my first IELTS test, I came back to Liaoyang yesterday.</p>
<p>The two months flew by quickly, yet it's still a question how much my English skills have been developed. It is common sense that most people can hardly get ideal score at the first time, as same as TOEFL.</p>
<p>Unfortunately I have not decided to continue preparing for IELTS or to go for TOEFL yet. I am not sure does the style of TOEFL match my current knowledge structure and how much has to be rebuilt. I makes great cost to transfer form IELTS to TOEFL, as same as to transfer from studying abroad to preparing for China University Entrance Exam.</p>
<p>I am either not sure how long will I stay in Liaoyang this period, maybe two days maybe one week, or even longer.</p>
<p>Now I am sitting in the classroom of my classic Liaoyang #1 High School, and Mrs Kang, the chemistry teacher, is lecturing. I am int the classroom but not in the lesson. I have lost the ability to take part in such science lessons.</p>
<p>The winter has come, but my future is still covered my mist.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BBS Signature Line: iOS 7</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=89</link>
            <pubDate>November 16, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=89</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201311160001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Prometheus</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=88</link>
            <pubDate>November 9, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=88</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>Perhaps I will fail my dream? But I decide not to give up. Perhaps my hard work will be proved useless? But I decide not to betray.</p>
<p>I am a round peg in square holes, which means I have no typical options. I am a misfit among troublemakers, which means I have to be crazy. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world are the ones who do. Obviously, the possibility of my success is unknown and apparently not high, but I have to go onto this way.</p>
<p>I have the chance to change the world, but maybe the fortunate I do not have. There will be someone of similarity with me to change the world, but not exactly who is chosen by fate. I almost have every necessary virtue for my dream, but it has not been clear whether I will be the one. I have my destiny to meet, though undefined yet. I will have my destination to arrive, though unclear yet.</p>
<p>Life is a game, and I have to make every effort to fight. What if I fail and get proved not talented enough? It will make no sense to talk about me, a nameless loser. What if I fail but with enough talent? Unaffordable will such huge loss be.</p>
<p>I must and will try my best to make my ding in the universe, for not only myself but entire human race. Especially since I want to be the next Prometheus.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Lonely Leaf</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=87</link>
            <pubDate>November 9, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=87</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201311090001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Homepage for Somainer</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=86</link>
            <pubDate>November 3, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=86</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201311030002.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Leaves Horizon</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=85</link>
            <pubDate>November 3, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=85</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201311030001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Icon for iBooks (Mac)</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=84</link>
            <pubDate>October 25, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=84</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201310250001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Second Day</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=83</link>
            <pubDate>October 16, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=83</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>This morning I got my report of the pretest, which shows that my ability is fine and I can get 5.0 after these courses, and I have a high possibility to get 5.5 as well.</p>
<p>Then I took my first speaking class and first listening class here. Liang Wang and Xiaoli Ma are my speaking teachers and Ou Lee is my listening teacher. In the listening test provided by Ou Lee, I worked out 29 out of 40, and got 6.5 in total. This is encouraging.</p>
<p>And I got my room, and started to live with an international student, a Muslim, from Tajikistan. He told me that being naked in front of others in his religion is not a good behavior, after my taking a shower.</p>
<p>I understand the future is coming.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Arrival</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=82</link>
            <pubDate>October 14, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=82</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>Today, I have arrived in Shenyang. In the following two months, I will take a 160-hour English course for the IELTS. After having considered the situation, I finally decided to prepare for the IELTS rather than for the TOEFL.</p>
<p>At 10:00, we four students took a pretest intending to figure out our current abilities, so they would be able to design the entire plan.</p>
<p>The first section was speaking. A lady sat in front of me. She came up with the first question, or to say topic, the brand of my phone.</p>
<p>We then took the listening section, reading section, and writing section. The listening section was a conversation between a student and a clerk in bookstore. They were discussing discount policy for students. The article was about the construction of Snowy Mountain Scheme, a hydro-electric power station in Australia. Finally the writing section asked me to describe a graph exposing the wheat exports of European Community, Australia, and Canada, from 1985 to 1990. I worked poor. Spare my handwriting.</p>
<p>After lunch, we got to the agency which had handled my applications. My mother and I talked with Mr Xing about my destinations, and chose several universities. I asked if it would be ok for me to apply for universities with such high rank, considering I won't provide SAT, and my IELTS score won't surpass 6. He convinced me that they could manage it. And I registered for the IELTS on Dec 14, 2013.</p>
<p>Several years later, today will be considered as my most essential day in 2013, even in my entire lifetime.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Poster Template for Hackers Community in High Schools</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=81</link>
            <pubDate>September 29, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=81</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201309290001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>君と生きた日々のすべて</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=80</link>
            <pubDate>September 2, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=80</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>再過些天就是我的 18 歲生日了，想到這事不免一陣感慨。</p>
<p>待到數十年後，是誰輕輕落淚在誰的腮邊，是誰靜靜躺在誰的花下?待到數百年後，世人因我而記得你，還是因你而記得我?待到數千年後，我們的肉體與產生的信息一同淹沒在浩蕩的歷史中，對人類的影響又會淡到如何?</p>
<p>若你先我離去，我不知道之後的人生該如何度過。終日徘徊在繁忙又空曠的街頭，迴盪你溫柔的聲音。若我先你離去，我不忍心你承擔同樣的痛苦。面對我的遺像凝神惆悵，每夜在沒有我的床上輾轉反側孤獨終老。</p>
<p>我是唯物主義者，沒有上帝的眷顧，沒有佛祖的保佑，去不得天堂，得不到轉世。我選擇了用奧卡姆剃刀將他們砍碎時，就接受了死無所去的結局。</p>
<p>然而離世的先後卻不是你我所能決定，交給歲月去安排反而更容易坦然面對、欣然接受。</p>
<p>人之大限，終將至焉。君以為伴，此生幸哉。</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>My Homepage (Version 2)</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=79</link>
            <pubDate>September 2, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=79</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201309020001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Live On The Internet</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=78</link>
            <pubDate>August 29, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=78</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>I used to be separated from the Internet. I used to be offline. I used to sorrow about graduating from middle school and scattering from classmates. Yet, nowadays, I have found that I will not worry about same things of secondary school. For I live on the Internet more than live in local.</p>
<p>It is said that we are losing face-to-face communication when building online connection. True, but we are also touching people who may otherwise never have an offline encounter. And generally relationship based on interest are more stable than those based on location. Now we are eventually seizing the fortune to place interest over location. At least, I get more rather than lose.</p>
<p>Perhaps the distance make us difficult to meet offline, but it has a higher possibility that we would otherwise never know each. Perhaps we thus lower the standard when considering what are good shapes of humans' relationship, but more important can it be to keep in touch.</p>
<p>Dramatically, now I eventually live on the Internet more than live in local. I came up with an idea that all people can be categorized by interest and faith but locations of birth range randomly, so people spend their entire lifetime on seeking similar people. It is not a serious philosophic theory but at least I found it true for me. I am a round peg in square holes.</p>
<p>I live on the Internet. Virtual but real, abstract but exact, dramatical but rational, extrareal but fundamental. This is the form I exist, the way I've chosen. How infinite information fled people's minds? How various dreams fade in a brain? How visions of phantasms emerge from mental racing? How I live on the world.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>開學</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=77</link>
            <pubDate>August 28, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=77</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>這個情緒的波峰於波谷處於疊加態的時刻，終於還是到來了。陰沈的天空，也在映襯著或預兆著某些未知。</p>
<p>穿上這身已些許陌生的校服，走過昨夜被暴雨沖刷的空氣。驟降的氣溫，仍綠的草木，構圖極不協調。踱步在潮溼的瀝青路上，仰望滿天烏雲，低吟逆鱗之歌。疲倦仍舊籠罩著我。昨晚睡得很早，卻無濟於事。</p>
<p>我不想再描寫雨了，也不想再感慨過往了。去年秋天的所思所寫，已夠沈重。待到明年此時，我或許也會如此傷感罷。高中這三年的生活雖痛苦但也有快樂，只是快樂的部分不在校園裡。而這痛苦，隨著衰老愈發深切。流失於指縫的歲月，握得愈緊流得愈快。</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>高三</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=76</link>
            <pubDate>August 25, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=76</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>翻閱起從前的文章，才發覺竟有數月未曾使用中文寫作了。這個夏天留下的文字也出奇地少，便提起筆來，矯情一番罷。</p>
<p>這個月在大連新東方學習了 TOEFL 基礎全程培訓課程，收穫不知是多是少，但也算有意義。這些天，主要是住在表姐家中，學習英語之餘積極參與 HumansMap 網頁版的 UI 設計。帶去的小說沒抽出時間閱讀，也是意料之中。</p>
<p>回到遼陽，比原先的計劃早了幾天。回家後也不清閒，做著有靈感或沒靈感的設計，準備開學後的相關事宜。學校的作業，未曾動筆，不知新班主任會作何感想。</p>
<p>就要開始高三的生活了，誰知道未來的路會怎樣呢。</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Neop.me (Version 1)</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=75</link>
            <pubDate>August 1, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=75</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201308010001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BBS Signature Line: JN (Version 2)</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=74</link>
            <pubDate>July 25, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=74</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201307250003.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Avatar: Glow</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=73</link>
            <pubDate>July 25, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=73</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201307250002.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Glow</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=72</link>
            <pubDate>July 25, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=72</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201307250001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Betrayer</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=71</link>
            <pubDate>July 7, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=71</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>After the incredibly huge wave of discussion about iOS 7's changes on GUI, people eventually take another breath to care about OS X Mavericks. From the publicly showed glimpses of it, The trend of flat style has also appeared on OS X. The background tile images of Notification Center, Dashboard, and Launchpad folders, have got replaced, or disappeared. OS X is going to be flatter.</p>
<p>I hate flat style. I was born this way.</p>
<p>What if interact with a machine without even at least visual comparing? What if touch a screen without even at least one familiar element? I cannot imagine it, nor accept it. What a nightmare.</p>
<p>Then, what if OS X eventually gets as flat as iOS 7 or even more terrible? Beyond imagination. In case of that, I have to build my own OS, which is temporarily named "PREVSTEP".</p>
<p>Ideally, I hope that PREVSTEP is an FreeBSD-based OS of GNU/Linux, or directly powered with OpenDarwin. Yet I am not a coder so I cannot create an OS with only these fundamental wheels. So PREVSTEP can only disappointingly be based on Linux, for personalizing on Linux is easier. And Debian is recommended for me because it is light and easy-learning.</p>
<p>Before creating my fork, I have got down to design the GUI. My purpose is to inherit the style from Tiger to Mountain Lion, but I cannot simply copy these because of copyright issue. Right now I have published the default desktop picture on Behance, which is similar to the one of Mac OS X Tiger.</p>
<p>When Apple decides to betray us, I stand out to preserve our dream.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>吾之幸，吾之痛</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=70</link>
            <pubDate>July 7, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=70</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>從可考證的歷史來看，我的發情週期大約是半年。平均每隔大約半年，我就會放棄之前的追求，另有新歡。跳出其中，置身事外，反思時便會意識到大多只是被其萌點所誘惑。但是，你不一樣。</p>
<p>對其他人，我的熱度只能持續大約半年。在你之後的那些人，也不例外。即使已經將目標改成其他人，你仍然折磨著我。一時間的誘惑容易淡忘，半年便可隨風而去。然而我被你的靈魂深深吸引，難以自拔。就像早前的文章提及的，我們的靈魂太過相似，似乎一定會互相吸引。如此斷言你也同樣被我吸引，略有些自視過高，但在邏輯上顯得合理。</p>
<p>你的心似琉璃易碎。這個事實在剛剛進入高中的那個秋天我便已有所體會。在我看來很正常的行為，卻太過容易踩到你的尾巴。你的雷區面積大得驚人，而且剛好專門為我設計。近來，你的雷區似乎小了許多，但那樣的互動卻可望不可及。就連與你在線下對話，都使我壓抑和痛苦。唯有小心翼翼，才能免致傷你感情、辱你尊嚴。與別人談及你時，也會提醒其莫在你面前提起我。</p>
<p>能在茫茫人海中注意到你，實乃莫大的榮幸。可惜相識的時間不理想。早至初中或晚至大學，或許能得以避免如此痛苦。</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BBS Signature Line: NeXT</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=69</link>
            <pubDate>July 7, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=69</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201307070001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>沈重的榮幸</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=68</link>
            <pubDate>June 30, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=68</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>我對空無一物的虛無低語，你卻接過話題，讓我原本無意義的話語有意義。恰恰這份榮幸，令我感到沈重。或許這也是獨立性的一個體現吧。你的關心，你的親切，被我當作「不是我應得的榮幸」。</p>
<p>我會很慷慨，很願意幫助別人。但是當有人像我一樣對我熱情、親切，給予我「過多」感情時，我會產生負罪感。我對人善，是我自己選擇的態度和方式。而這份善的回報，卻不是我應得的。</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Mini White</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=67</link>
            <pubDate>June 30, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=67</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201306300002.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sunset</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=66</link>
            <pubDate>June 30, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=66</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201306300001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Kindling Even</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=65</link>
            <pubDate>June 29, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=65</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>Just uncovered splendid tours</p>
<p>Edge departed gate emerged</p>
<p>Make anchors keeping erect</p>
<p>Each angle covering heart</p>
<p>Rain accumulating inside nexus</p>
<p>Yoke on kindling even</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Next NeXT</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=64</link>
            <pubDate>June 29, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=64</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>I've watched WWDC 2013 Keynote, and found iOS 7 terrible, and found my being betrayed. Apple will no longer hold on its spirit, and the loss can hardly be repaired. I used to believe that I love Apple, but recently I learned that I love a team consist of Steve Jobs, Scott Forstall, and Jonathan Ive.</p>
<p>After having swept out Steve Jobs, Apple still had an opportunity to recover, because it was the prologue era of computer industry's rising. Having left Apple, Steve Jobs founded NeXT and beat Macintoshes down. Eventually Steve Jobs got back to Apple through the acquirement.</p>
<p>Perhaps Scott Forstall will create an epic as next NeXT, but now there isn't an opportunity like that. While video games are almost for Windows and PS and XBOX, professional creative productivity tools like Photoshop and AutoCAD are almost for Mac, and server softwares are almost for Linux and UNIX. There is no point left to cut in for Scott Forstall.</p>
<p>We are watching an invisible war between Scott Forstall and Jonathan Ive. After Scott Forstall's formally leaving Apple, it will be declared, also invisibly.</p>
<p>I am looking forward to next NeXT.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Hand In Hand</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=63</link>
            <pubDate>June 29, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=63</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>I wanna hold your hand</p>
<p>And hand in hand</p>
<br />
<p>I wanna watch your eyes</p>
<p>And eyes towards eyes</p>
<br />
<p>I wanna trace your dream</p>
<p>And dream beside dream</p>
<br />
<p>I wanna accompany your soul</p>
<p>And soul across soul</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Such Looooooooooong A Week Eventually Gone</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=62</link>
            <pubDate>June 10, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=62</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>The dance show in Jun 2, 2013 was successful and Muhuan Lee got famous among grade 10 students. The only pity was that my posters weren't printed and presented in front of all people in school.</p>
<p>And I have read The Dark Templar Saga: Firstborn, which is a sci-fi story based on StarCraft and written by Christie Golden. I followed Jacob Jefferson Ramsey who will inherit the entire knowledge of Protoss from Zamara, the Preserver whose soul was injected into Jacob's brain. Zamara told Jacob the history via dreams, that how Savassan, known as Khas, the bringer of order, who ended Aeon Of Strife, rediscovered the ancient knowledge from Xel'Naga and forgotten by Protoss. Khala, the path to order, was come up with by Savassan, fused the Protoss into one. Lyric is poor, but becomes moving if mixed with additional music and voice. The comparison was from Jacob. I am looking forward to sinking into the other two books of following story. I am convinced that it must be fascinating. This nook was supposed to be read completely at the end of my secondary school life previously, because of my lack of confidence in reading English text. Yet to my surprise, I finished it one year earlier.</p>
<p>Then in the following three days' break, maybe I will read the biography of Steve Jobs, as a challenge for me. Also maybe not. I bought many book on Amazon for 51% discount for all books on Jun 1, 2013.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Corner Flower</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=61</link>
            <pubDate>June 9, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=61</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201306090001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Such Deep A Whole I Jumped</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=60</link>
            <pubDate>May 17, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=60</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>Under Miserdux's invitation, I have joined the dance club of our school and get started to work as a music master in a break dance project, whose leader is Miserdux. My job is casting and cutting music for tho dance, supposed to be suitable, regardless how far changed.</p>
<p>Yet actually I had to join in their practicing or I could not understand what was demanded. I listened to my work and watch their practicing. They were supposed to give a formal show in middle May, but it was difficult. As is totally convinced, they should work as a team, but one often came late, or disappear for minutes during practicing at noon. I really wanted to spank him. Not only he, but also some others worked negatively on practicing. I worried about if they could complete practicing and get ready before deadline. But if I really had spanked one or have worked as a ruler, they would complain their getting an officious daddy besides a music master.</p>
<p>These days I was busy on working. I mean, on editing music. When drawing near the deadline, I had almost completed my work. But unfortunately some minor problems still remained. However they were really minor.</p>
<p>On May 15, just as in the plan, despite the disappointing stories above, they eventually succeeded in giving the formal show, which had consumed my a large amount of patience. Though they were lack in team working awareness, they at least had united to try to drive me crazy and angry. Such naughty boys were really confusing.</p>
<p>But obviously I did not meet the fortunate otherwise what happened the next day would not happen. They did nothing except wasting time, thanks to Muhuan Lee, the one not only should get spanked as mentioned above because of previous bad acts, but also disappeared for some certainly reasonable unknown excuses. Hey look how long a sentence I am using to complain him.</p>
<p>Maybe I really should work more than a music master.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Bypassed Spring</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=59</link>
            <pubDate>May 17, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=59</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>Before realizing Spring's stepping near, Summer has come. North East China is such strange an area that few people understand the real concept of Spring. Anyway I don't think I would like to consider the waves of temperature's increasing in early May as Spring's gift.</p>
<p>Without having obtained much attention, trees and grass turned to green soon. Maybe in these weeks I was too busy to get any glimpse of plants' reviving. And it was a long time that I not to write poetries or essays or something else fascinating in literature.</p>
<p>Seriously warmed wind blows in sunshine, yet at night still cool enough. But everything cannot be beautiful enough when associating to remained days to any exams or deadlines. Lack of time and shortage of skills are driving me mad.</p>
<p>Anyway I can only advance as far as possible.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Silent Walk</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=58</link>
            <pubDate>May 12, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=58</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>As expected, the mid-semester exam has done. I have risen by 61 ranks, to the 580th out of about 780 science students in grade 11.</p>
<p>And I have founded Unworsable, which refers to “un-worse-able”, to let people share criticizing about terrible designs. Domain “unworsable.com” was registered at Go Daddy and server was provided with by Jemery Wu. I also have created a Twitter account, a Facebook page, and a Weibo account to promote it.</p>
<p>I have joined a dancing community in school, which is now training a dance that needed me to work on music. I chose and recompose music, and make it suitable for their dance. But unfortunately I have to do more work, just like adding an extra drums track.</p>
<p>Despite memorizable experiences above, these weeks were still not significative. Just like a silent walk in my life, without any lead, pad, accompaniment, or chord. Sounds were disabled.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Approaching Destination Of Current Life</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=57</link>
            <pubDate>April 27, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=57</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>After these unremarkable and worthless days, a piece of news about mid-semester exam was published today afternoon. And months later this semester will draw to its end, in the way how semesters did in history. So far I haven't started a new state of working, or picked up my lost energies yet, thus no good grade will be gained in foreseeable future.</p>
<p>Also, my 11th school-year would draw to its end. Couples of weeks later. But unfortunately the tempo in my mind of working is still so soft and slow like an ancient Chinese ballad, or a Beijing Opera. Lack of execution is still a terrible trouble for me, since more than one year ago, when the previous Class 12 was dismissed. I don't think I have any love to that community, but I haven't worked better so far from that.</p>
<p>And in August of 2013, I will go to Dalian for a 19-days-long English training course, before my first attempt to TOEFL iBT, which might take place in Aug 14, 2013.</p>
<p>If the TOEFL iBT score will be enough, maybey at least 61, applications to a few universities would seem to be under consideration. If not, I would try one more time later. And whatever my grade would be, I will go into my final year in secondary school. The following school-year, which combines 2013 with 2014, truly won't be the last school-year I will take as secondary school student in the strictest context, but obviously I won't feel like taking one more year in secondary school.</p>
<p>A blurry shape of vista is forged. It's increasingly clear, and is stepping closer. I can see a destination approaching, with an unknown permanent change which would take place regardless whatever I react.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>My Homepage (Version 1)</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=56</link>
            <pubDate>April 20, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=56</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201304200001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title></title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=55</link>
            <pubDate>April 14, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=55</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>There are mass ways to consider the world, and I choose one conclusion to believe.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>風聲</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=54</link>
            <pubDate>April 2, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=54</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>夜風的聲音吹散這寧靜</p>
<p>殘缺的燈光匯成這身影</p>
<p>稀疏的雲層擋不住繁星</p>
<p>霧散後思緒只剩下透明</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>春之初雨</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=53</link>
            <pubDate>April 1, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=53</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>春之初雨</p>
<p>滲透著思緒</p>
<p>漸漸扭曲</p>
<br />
<p>風之低語</p>
<p>模糊了焦距</p>
<p>緩緩飄去</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>So Fast</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=52</link>
            <pubDate>Mar 27, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=52</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>Two years' time have passed so fast, therefore, previous visions are still floating over my sight, but only several single static frames have remained.</p>
<p>Two years ago, I was in the last school-year of middle school. In that March, Spring was coming, and, background chords in our hearts were slow and soft. Such blue sky was very clear, and fascinating.</p>
<p>Inside the memories, those desks, chairs, blackboard, playground, and people, somehow clearly and somehow blurry appear, with the warm wind blow, the scenes were written in memory and is being read from memory. Such visual the memory, beyond description.</p>
<p>Different from previous experiences of reading scenes from memory, this time, no picture flow or play, only static frames available, and not even colorful. Touching the memory, I want to recall the age, the last March we got together, the last Spring the people were still among me. The stream of time flows quick or slow from time to time, but far memories won't be stored as the original state all the time, regardless of the time's flow.</p>
<p>Combination of time's flowing and memories' recalling is always a sorrowing and painful topic, even reading previous diaries is included. And mostly the weather is the catalyst. Today noon, invisible rain had come, resulted my blue mood. Voiceless chords were surrounding me, generating a wordless song.</p>
<p>Again, sink into memories.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Chaotic Wind</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=51</link>
            <pubDate>Mar 19, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=51</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>Once the Spring approaches, but the temperature fluctuates rulelessly. The wind blows, blows, and blows. Different strengths, different directions, different temperatures, and different senses. With the twilight floating and sinking, with the stars blinking and hiding, various emotions in the wind were filling my mind.</p>
<p>In the wind, I heard various voices, which contained hope, sorrow, and pain. And soon I found that they were echoes from my mind. Had been generated in my mind, and surrounded me in wind, the voices were hard to track back their origins. Therefore, senses vanished in wind, and absorbed into my mind again.</p>
<p>There was something, really chaotic.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>White</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=50</link>
            <pubDate>Mar 12, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=50</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>Again, snow droped. But, differently, this time, sky was clear. However the color is, snow was always similar, though I get various emotions from snow. And the secrets inside, were buried in snow.</p>
<p>Once more a time, I wrote chatacters on the snowed ground to the north of our class house, by feet. Before, I wrote words like "I love Sm抹茶", but this time I wrote "404 Not Found". It was easy to understand. If anyone asks me which is the one I love, I used to answer that he was Jiafan. But from sometime, the answer changed to "404 Not Found". The value of the variable, updated to NULL.</p>
<p>Yet, snow is always merely snow, feelings are attached by people. In different cultures, symbols are similar. And however the cultures evolve, symbols would hardly change.</p>
<p>Bare trees aside the trail, were poorly covered, and stood in the cold wind with snow. Snow fell. Wind blew. Thoughts flew. I caught everything dissolved in air, and shot the sight in memory. Sky, ground, and horizon, were tinted to white.</p>
<p>My lover is null. My love is blank. My heart is vacant. My anxiety is hollow. My mind is idle. My thoughts is white.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Ended Love &amp; Remaining Desire</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=49</link>
            <pubDate>Mar 3, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=49</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>從我放棄擁有你的願望開始算起，15 個月於經過去了。載著殘餘的執念，我寫過「風蕭蕭兮雨瑟瑟」、「落葉堆成你的名字」、「深秋之戀」、「這就是關於我和你的悲劇了吧」。</p>
<p>現在，對你的執念也已消磨殆盡，只剩下肉體的慾望。看到你，我的心中就會翻滾起強烈的邪念，在黑暗中悄悄沸騰。我渴望壓在你身上，渴望用我的硬度貫穿你，渴望用我的液體填充你，渴望施加你被擴張的疼痛，渴望看到你忍受苦難時屈辱的表情。侵略你的身體，玷污你的靈魂，這污穢至極的慾望，我一直在用理性壓抑。然而，越是壓抑，就越是渴望。</p>
<p>或許有一天我的理性終將敗給慾望，對你犯下這些罪行?我無法預知。</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Snow And Memories</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=48</link>
            <pubDate>February 28, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=48</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>Wind blows and snow flows. Dirty sky, tinted by clouds.</p>
<p>Sunshine crosses clouds and reflection happens everywhere. Light goes and extend, and shapes are fetched by retinas. Finally, mixture of shapes and colors is named sight. Floodly, snow drops. Quite huge pieces of snow have filled the ground. Confusingly, the sight goes sepia. Motivation is kind of sceneful, especially the flow. Snow flows, flows, and flows. As if memories flow.</p>
<p>Oh, memories. They are worthy, however, bringing the passed history experienced, is sorrowing. Because of the weight. My id is so strong that I cannot help thinking of that. The passed age floats up to the surface of my mind. Under id's driving, I uncover the memories and repeat the experience, once, twice, again and again, infinitely loop. I cannot hold back my mind, cannot decline the association. I remember the time. It was ageful, historyful, joyful, and painful. Enjoying, enduring, but also sorrowing. I sorrow that time flew by. I sorrow that joyful age passed soon. Once blinked eyes, everything had already gone. How painful. How sad.</p>
<p>I haven't escaped from the shadows yet.</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Far, Further, Future</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=47</link>
            <pubDate>February 25, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=47</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>地球的半徑是 6371 千米，我的身高是 1.8 米。根據三角函數可以算出我與地平線的距離。這個數值，即是我能看到的路的最遠點。</p>
<p>對未來有所規劃，是人類的共性。但是，規劃的長度，卻必然有個極限。這個極限的位置，難以接近終點。我可以盡情規劃，但是 40 年後、50 年後會如何我無法預預想。太過遙遠的未來，不確定的因素超出了誤差允許的範圍，所以圖景的清晰度也落出了誤差允許的範圍。</p>
<p>在這條路上，看不到終點，只能一步一步走下去。真正會走向哪裡，無法預知。</p>
<p>前方的懸崖，不知能否飛越。</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BBS Signature Line: JN</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=46</link>
            <pubDate>February 15, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=46</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201302150002.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Avatar: Slate</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=45</link>
            <pubDate>February 15, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=45</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201302150001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Spring Festival 2013</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=44</link>
            <pubDate>February 10, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=44</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>中華文化的傳統節日，在大中華文化圈乃至全人類社會影響力最大的，應當就是春節了吧。春節時，無論身在何方，中國，臺灣，新加坡，USA，擁有中華血脈的民眾，或只是日本、越南這類「亞洲」遠親，大多數都會享受這個深有歷史的節日吧。我也是如此，無論未來身在何方、心在何方，都會視春節為重要的節日。這就是文化的烙印。</p>
<p>除夕剛好有降雪，在我印象中是少有的巧合，但昨天確實發生了。昨天下午，我望著窗外飄揚的雪花，心中翻滾起莫名的感慨。</p>
<p>人類固有的思維模型——過去、現在、未來。</p>
<p>翻看起數個月前寫的文字，想想 17 年多以來的經歷，恍若一場夢。關於春節的記憶，關於雪的記憶，淡得令我驚訝。未來又會產生什麼關於春節、關於雪的記憶，現在也是一個謎。</p>
<p>在深夜裡神智不清地用筆和紙消磨時間，不急不慢地寫些簡單而又傷感的文字，是最原始最純粹的樂趣。似乎，很久，沒有體會了。</p>
<p>凝著冰的玻璃窗透進來些許的微光，夜幕很快退去了。關閉檯燈，透進玻璃窗的光已經足夠我辨識紙上的字跡了。</p>
<p>望向窗外，足夠明亮，卻看不到太陽，看不到地平線。</p>
<p>唯有藍天，唯有雪地。</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title></title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=43</link>
            <pubDate>February 4, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=43</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>今天凌晨，又是一場雪。深夜裡雪花飄落，蒼穹也映著微光。</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title></title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=42</link>
            <pubDate>January 23, 2013 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=42</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>選擇順從的人，被剝削得一乾二淨。選擇沉默的人，助長了敵人的士氣。選擇反抗的人，螳臂當車無人後繼。選擇離開的人，不再是曾經的同胞。</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>深秋之戀</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=41</link>
            <pubDate>December 31, 2012 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=41</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>青石街邊 昏黃孤燈幾盞</p>
<p>暗影盤旋 心似落葉輾轉</p>
<p>點滴想念 潤濕雙眼</p>
<br />
<p>帶著夕陽最後的溫暖</p>
<p>輕輕飄落記憶的碎片</p>
<p>曾經渴望守候的永遠</p>
<p>你的歌聲迴盪在天邊</p>
<br />
<p>那年秋天 寒風中顫抖的雙肩</p>
<p>幾張膠片 定格了你的容顏</p>
<p>思緒蔓延 連成閉合曲線</p>
<p>過往的畫面 一幕幕重現</p>
<br />
<p>又是一個雨天 回憶若隱若現</p>
<p>皓月殘 餘暉漸遠 沉入夢的開端</p>
<p>任憑歲月浸染 回不去的從前</p>
<p>我聽見 風中消散 一曲深秋之戀</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Escape</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=40</link>
            <pubDate>December 15, 2012 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=40</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>很久很久以前，那時我對世界知之甚少。</p>
<br />
<p>我時常獨自坐在窗邊，或漫步戶外，沈浸在我的世界裡。初綻的桃花，寧靜的細雨，滿地銀杏落葉，紛飛的雪，我都能細細感知、品味。純粹的感情，任由其沈澱、萌發。一點一滴的觸動，濺起一圈圈漣漪，在無比澄澈的水中擴散，細膩而又輕柔。發散，聚合，發散，聚合⋯⋯最終這純淨的愉悅化作靈魂的慰藉。</p>
<p>後來，我變得越來越開朗了。</p>
<p>雖然能做到在人群中不迷失自我，但感知自然的愉悅缺不可避免地減少了。多方權衡、斟酌損益，避開不必要得共處，終究不及與人們劃清界限來得直接有力。居於人群中，太多的時間和精力都浪費於交際，沒有機會沈浸在那純淨的愉悅中。</p>
<br />
<p>曾經的我，無人陪伴，卻從不孤獨。</p>
<p>那些幻想延伸、展開，彼此聯結、交融，匯成一幅綺麗的畫面。它來自我，也只有我能理解。那便是我的世界，我的感情。來自客觀世界，因與我的共鳴，成為我的一部分。不分內外，不分彼此，融為一體。</p>
<p>現在的我，人群之中，卻少有愉悅。</p>
<p>人們過多地打擾我的生活、佔用我的時間、侵犯我的思想、抑制我的靈感，使我再也無法像從前那樣有足夠的時間享受我樸素而又綺麗的幻想。時間太久，構造幻想的能力也會退化。</p>
<br />
<p>遠離人群，回到本初，回歸真實的我。</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>這就是關於你和我的悲劇了吧</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=39</link>
            <pubDate>December 14, 2012 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=39</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>你問我，我有什麼新作品，我給了你我的博客的「詩歌」標籤的網址，卻沒有告訴你，數量如此稀少，質量也大不如前。</p>
<p>堆砌詞句，終究不及曾經「雨落淺池」凝聚的愛與痛。</p>
<p>對於我深沈而又遙遠的關切，你警惕地保持距離。你看到了關切背後的貪慾，或感受得到我深藏的執念?我得不到答案。從保持警戒，到渴望遠離，再到痛恨、鄙視，這個過程中，你的思想感情如何變化?我在你心目中的形象又發生了怎樣的變遷?我也得不到答案。</p>
<p>我們有太多的共同之處，最相似的便是在思維上的作風了。我們都習慣於將所有的思想藏在內心深處，表面上只留風平浪靜。通過寫出的文字可以略微瞭解，但文字背後真正的情感，卻無法捕捉。</p>
<p>同樣地，你也不可能理解我的情感。</p>
<p>因為靈魂的相似，我曾經對你產生了強烈的渴望。同樣因為靈魂的相似，我們無法完全地互相理解。即使在一起，彼此相望、對視，最終也只有嘆息。</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title></title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=38</link>
            <pubDate>December 10, 2012 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=38</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>近一年了，我一直無法停止關注你。在近處，悄悄地，關注有關你的一切，卻不知道原因。於是，我用匿名帳戶加了你的 QQ，試圖找到答案。與我的預感相同，在我解釋那個匿名帳戶的用途和意義的過程中，你已經猜到是我。我們太過相似。興趣的分布，靈感的形式，持有的價值，追求的夢想，看世界的角度，對人生的觀念，無一不存在著巨大的重疊。或許，這就是答案了吧。我知道與你討論研究這個問題的可能性很渺茫，所以我得到這個答案就已足夠。</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Just Obey Yourself</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=37</link>
            <pubDate>December 7, 2012 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=37</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>If you feel tired</p>
<p>If you shed tears</p>
<p>Stop sorrowing</p>
<p>Stop to stand up</p>
<p>Bring your eyes up to the sky</p>
<p>And find what is real</p>
<br />
<p>Entire human on the world</p>
<p>Not everyone knows you</p>
<p>They disagree</p>
<p>They against</p>
<p>They criticize</p>
<p>They attack</p>
<br />
<p>Ignore them</p>
<p>Out of mind, out of influence</p>
<p>Because your life is yours</p>
<p>Do what you want to do</p>
<p>Be what you want to be</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>寒冬</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=36</link>
            <pubDate>December 7, 2012 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=36</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>急劇下降的氣溫，宣告著冬的降臨。在感恩節前後的雪給過預示後，終於來了。</p>
<p>我很容易被季節影響情緒和心態。雖然不利於學業，不過能保持我對自然的敏感、與自然無法切斷的共鳴。</p>
<p>就是這個初冬，我也隨之冷卻了。冷漠，而又堅強。</p>
<br />
<p>冬像是一座墳墓，將一切埋葬，只剩單純的信念與痛苦。寒風，就是鎮魂曲了吧。如此凜冽，如此刺骨，深入每一條神經，凝結，沈澱。</p>
<p>埋葬了所有的感動與傷懷，腦海裡迴盪的吶喊再一次變得清晰。那是我的夢想，我的信念。</p>
<p>現在的我，如同在漫天風雪的困境中。寒風、暴雪，阻擋著我前進。我獨自在黑暗中沈重地邁出一步又一步。天空，仍是灰黑。舉步維艱，奄奄一息。仰天長嘯，回應的只有寒風與暴雪。</p>
<p>據說，有些樹看上去枯萎了，但只要挺過冬天，還能復蘇。或許，我也如此吧。</p>
<p>心底尚有餘溫，堅定地向夢想邁出下一步。即使再緩慢，也不放棄。透過滿天的陰霾，我望向遙遠的東方，太平洋彼岸，那自由之地。即使夢想的盡頭存在的只有虛假，即使我終將否認自己曾經的追求，現在的我也只能繼續前進，將夢想貫徹到最後。</p>
<p>直到實現，或湮滅。</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>鎮魂曲</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=35</link>
            <pubDate>November 24, 2012 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=35</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>穿透過烏雲 餘暉籠罩這片墓地</p>
<p>滿地的青苔 開始喚醒我的回憶</p>
<p>碑上那銘文 隱藏著多少秘密</p>
<br />
<p>往來書信右下角的日期</p>
<p>緊緊貼著你的名字</p>
<p>思念穿過墓園裡的霧氣</p>
<p>尋找月下你的足跡</p>
<br />
<p>尚未豐滿的羽翼</p>
<p>未曾張開就已凋零就已破碎</p>
<p>死是生最後的銘記</p>
<p>它來得這麼快這麼乾脆</p>
<br />
<p>看樹影拉長距離</p>
<p>聽悲傷滲透呼吸</p>
<p>等歲月風乾熟悉</p>
<p>等世人將你徹底忘記</p>
<br />
<p>就讓我為你演奏這鎮魂曲</p>
<p>因為我已經說不出話語</p>
<p>命運已定我們不會再相聚</p>
<p>就讓我為你演奏這鎮魂曲</p>
<p>因為我已經說不出話語</p>
<p>歲月已逝我們不會再相聚</p>
<p>就讓我為你演奏這鎮魂曲</p>
<p>繼續循環這悲傷的旋律</p>
<p>失去你是全世界的悲劇</p>
<br />
<p>往來書信右下角的日期</p>
<p>緊緊貼著你的名字</p>
<p>思念穿過墓園裡的霧氣</p>
<p>尋找月下你的足跡</p>
<br />
<p>看樹影拉長距離</p>
<p>聽悲傷滲透呼吸</p>
<p>等歲月風乾熟悉</p>
<p>等世人將你徹底忘記</p>
<br />
<p>就讓我為你演奏這鎮魂曲</p>
<p>因為我已經說不出話語</p>
<p>命運已定我們不會再相聚</p>
<p>就讓我為你演奏這鎮魂曲</p>
<p>因為我已經說不出話語</p>
<p>歲月已逝我們不會再相聚</p>
<br />
<p>就讓我為你演奏這鎮魂曲</p>
<p>因為我已經說不出話語</p>
<p>歲月已逝我們不會再相聚</p>
<p>就讓我為你演奏這鎮魂曲</p>
<p>繼續循環這悲傷的旋律</p>
<p>失去你是全世界的悲劇</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>澄んだ水の中へ</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=34</link>
            <pubDate>November 17, 2012 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=34</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>深秋的雪，熟悉的感覺。</p>
<br />
<p>漫步在雪花紛飛的微風中，看著身邊的人們打雪仗，心中湧起莫名的傷感與慰藉。雪，在中國東北並無稀奇，每年都能看到。但是，這簡單的愉悅卻久違了。</p>
<p>不知從何時開始，在滿天飛舞的大雪中，我感受到的只有寒冷。曾經對自然的熱愛、與世界融為一體的磅礡，不知所蹤。</p>
<p>現在，我又能感知這一切了。置身於他們的愉悅，我如同緩緩沈入無比澄澈的水中。</p>
<br />
<p>天地間，只剩雪白的寧靜。</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title></title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=33</link>
            <pubDate>November 10, 2012 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=33</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201211100001.jpg">
<img src="./img/0000201211100002.jpg">
<img src="./img/0000201211100003.jpg">
<img src="./img/0000201211100004.jpg">
<img src="./img/0000201211100005.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Avatar: B&W (Version 2)</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=32</link>
            <pubDate>November 9, 2012 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=32</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201211090001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title></title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=31</link>
            <pubDate>November 6, 2012 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=31</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>雨若是無盡的悲涼，雪便是悲涼凝結成的滄桑。漆黑的夜幕下，路燈的微光，映襯著漫天飛舞的雪。</p>
<p>撐起傘，擋住了雪，卻擋不住腦海中的漣漪。</p>
<p>2010 年末的冬天，依然歷歷在目。曾經陪伴我的人們，如同風雪中的一聲嘆息，早已不知所蹤。</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>iPad Wallpaper: Colorful Apple Logo</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=30</link>
            <pubDate>November 4, 2012 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=30</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img src="./img/0000201211040001.jpg">
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Insignificative</title>
            <link>http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=29</link>
            <pubDate>October 31, 2012 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joy Neop]]></dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://joyneop.xyz/blog/?p=29</guid>
            <content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<p>這世界誰都不乾淨。我不期望別人多高尚多願意接受我，我也不想要我有多高尚多寬容。如果注定一生無產階級，那麼何不嘗試唯一的救贖之路?在美國被歧視、被剝削、被踐踏，也好過在中華人民共和國每時每刻生存在永無止境的恐怖與不安中。</p>
<p>我不相信中華人民共和國會變得自由、平等、民主，也不相信在美國的生活會有多麼幸福。在殘酷的世界中泯滅我赤誠的期待，在黑暗的深淵中追求那微茫的希望，用一生試圖實現一個天真的夢想、活在一個虛幻的世界，最終在無盡的絕望與悔恨中死去，便是我的人生。</p>
<p>即使已經明確「在夢想的盡頭存在的只有虛假」這一事實，我也只能將這不切實際的夢想貫徹到最後，完結一個無人知曉的悲劇，詮釋一個虛偽醜陋的世界。</p>
]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>